Rob Kirkpatrick

Data Analyst

(423) 836-1132 | RobKirk3@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/robkirk3/ | github.com/RobKirk3 | Nashville, TN

ABOUT ME

I turn messy data into clean, compelling stories. Whether as a business operations specialist cleaning data or entertaining crowds as a musician, knowing what is important to my audience is critical. Data analytics lets me take my skills and do interesting, valuable work.

SKILLS

SQL | Postgres Python Data Visualization | Dashboard Power BI | Tableau Excel | Pivot Tables GitHub

EDUCATION

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

Data Analytics Bootcamp Expected Graduation: May 2021

BELMONT UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Music

EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYTICS APPRENTICE

Nashville Software School, Nashville, TN January 2021 - Present

Nashville Software School is a non-profit whose mission is to grow the tech community in the Nashville area

- <u>Property Code Violations</u> Map built in Jupyter Notebooks exploring residential property code violations in my zip code
- <u>Nuclear Energy in America 2019</u> PowerBI dashboard exploring how much Nuclear Energy different states produced in 2019
- <u>Dueling Piano Songs</u> Tableau dashboard exploring most important Dueling Piano songs for a performer to learn

DUELING PIANO ENTERTAINER

Freelance

July 2015 - Present

- Entertain at weddings, corporate events, parties, bars, and more
- Perform hundreds of musically diverse songs

OPERATIONS SERVICES SENIOR SPECIALIST

ServiceSource, Nashville, TN June 2011 - October 2015

- Successfully ran a Lead Generation Pilot Project for Johnson Controls that led to over \$350k additional revenue for client within an 11 month period
- Delivered process documents, call scripts, email templates, and reason codes for Johnson Controls to use for the Lead Generation program internally
- Past projects include Data Cleanup, Data Governance, and Sales Bookings within the Microsoft Dynamics CRM
- Consistently recognized by management for excellent performance, including the "Legend of the Quarter" award for Q2 2015